Woke up feeling like I'm 90 years old My back's on fire, my story's been dulled Used to bounce back like a rubber band snap Now it's two full days of this recovering trap Two day hangover, it used to be one The party's still fun, but the cottage is done I paid double the price for my good time run Two day hangover, it used to be one
West I could heal up, felt like a great plan This morning I'm dying, can't eat instead Care of the dog, but the dog bit back Now I'm trapped in a cycle of panic attack Today hangover, it used to be one The shots were so smooth, now I'm under the gun I party like a fool, but the morning's no fun Today hangover, it used to be one
Used to dance all done, no care in my head Now I'm boobling remedies from the operative bed Feels like Gatorade can't make this right Guess I'll feel normal by Tuesday night
The cloth's my enemy, time's not my friend Can't stop the party, but I can't pretend Cute was a blessing, I never did see Now it's two day payback for every spree